(Amy:)but I'm guessing
still angry?
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
(Bernadette:)My boss wants to meet with me,
and I'm stressing.
(Amy:)You really think they're gonna
start treating you differently?
(Bernadette:)Are you kidding?
(Bernadette:)I've always been
treated differently!
Look at me!
Listen to me!
(Bernadette:)I mean, the first thought
when you see me isn't,
"That's a scientist."
It's, "I wonder if her mommy
knows where she is."
(Amy:)I am really regretting
that I got you a Happy Meal.
(Bernadette:)I've worked so hard
to get where I am,
(Bernadette:)and I don't want
to get sent back to square one
(Bernadette:)because I'm pregnant.
(Amy:)I understand how you feel.
(Colonel Williams:)Thank you.
(Amy:)I wish there were
(Amy:)some way I could make it better.
(Bernadette:)Well, you brought me
French fries. That's a start.
(Amy:)Uh, actually, I got you apple
slices 'cause you're pregnant.
(Bernadette:)Apple slices?
(Bernadette:)What kind of lunatic goes
to McDonald's and gets fruit?!
(Amy:)I'll be right back.
And a chocolate shake!